A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Office of Communications and Public Affairs, News Releases, Series 1 FA223
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Office of Communications and Public Affairs, News Releases, Series 1
1954-1990
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA223
0.44 Cubic Feet 1 box
1 box.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 365-1
Scope and Contents
News releases excluding those issued in connection with Program Planning and Development.
Arrangement
Chronological
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment. Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for scholarly research.
Public relations; Rockefeller University; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
- 1954-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)